

About me

I am a graduate Computer Science student at Manchester Metropolitan University with vast experience in hospitality. I'm certain that my distinctive life experience paired with my hospitality work has provided me with the skill set required to adapt to any working place.

I am highly organised and dedicated, hardworking individual with amazing interpersonal skills as well as team skills and strive for success and efficiency.

Personal Details

Date of Birth March 20, 1995

Nationality

Languages

Portuguese

English

Matheus

Undergraduate Computer Student



Fraser Street, Swinton, Manchester



matheuscpozzobon@gmail.com



+44 7476 711746

Work Experience

ALBERTS SHED

Manchester Nov 2021 - Present Waiter

THE BLACK FRIAR

Manchester Aug 2021 - Nov 2021 Waiter

JIMMY'S KILLER PRAWNS

Manchester Feb 2021 - Aug 2021 Waiter/Supervisor

GRAND PACIFIC

Manchester Sept 2018 - Oct 2020 Waiter

ALBERT'S WORSLEY

Manchester Sept 2017 - Sept 2018 Waiter

THE BLIND PIG

Manchester Mar 2017 - Sept 2017 **Bartender**

CLIFF TOWN HOUSE

Dublin May 2016 - Sept 2016 Cashier

WRIGHTS FOOD FAYRE

Dublin Jul 2015 - Apr 2016 Waiter

SAMBO SUSHI

Porto Alegre March 2014 - Feb 2015 Waiter

Waiter assistant/Waiter

300 COSMO DINING

ROOM

Porto Alegre Jun 2013 - Feb 2014



matheuscpozzobon.com



github.com/mattpozzobon



linkedin.com/in/mattpozzobon

Education

MANCHESTER METROPOLITAN UNIVERSITY

Manchester 2022

Bachelor Level, A 1st

Skills

Python

C#

Java

Courses

ISE (The Internation School of English)

Dublin

2016

DELFIN LANGUAGE SCHOOL

Dublin 2015 English

Level, Lower Advanced

English

Level, Upper-Intermediate

Projects

ONLINE MULTIPLAYER BATTLE GAME

Python

(Sockets, Multiprocessing, Threads, OpenCV, Mediapipe, among other libraries)

An Online Multiplayer Game I've created to include hand gesture recognition to interact with your character. This was my final year project for Manchester Metropolitan University.

A link demonstrating the project can be seen bellow: https://youtu.be/1pnPoetKL_0